Gonzalo Cuellar Aliaga

Full Stack Developer

Puerto Varas, Chile +56 9 5665 9732 gonzaliaga@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/gonzalo-cuellar-aliaga/ github.com/gonzaliaga

In my career as a Web Developer and BackEnd Developer, I have carried out work in various areas, always focusing on my expertise in: React, NodeJS, JS, ExpressJS, Firebase, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, and Frameworks. I have led and managed teams and have been part of units in Development, Communications, Home Automation, and AI. This has allowed me to develop skills in Leadership, Assertive Communication, Problem Solving, Adaptability, and, above all, to continuously learn and stay at the forefront of technologies. English Level: B1 Intermediate.

PROJECTS

Full Stack Web Developer - Parcels (06/2023 - 07/2023)

- Designed and developed an E-commerce platform for land parcel sales, including features such as Login, Dashboard, interaction with Google maps, among other functionalities for purchasing a land parcel – Payment Gateway.
- Technologies used: NextJs, Redux-Toolkit, Tailwind TypeScript MongoDB.
- Project link: parcelas.vercel.app
- Video link: https://vimeo.com/848581733?share=copy

Full Stack Web Developer – Imperial Fast Foods (09/2023 – in progress)

- Designed and developed an E-commerce platform for fast food sales, including user registration, local and third-party (Google Mail) login, Admin Dashboard, interfaces for Waitstaff, Kitchen, Cashier, as well as online orders and Google Maps integration for order tracking. Payment Gateway.
- Technologies used: VUE, JS, Tailwind, Firebase.
- Repository link: github.com/gonzaliaga/imperial-comidas.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Teaching Assistant - HENRY (06/2023 - 10/2023)

- Coordinated a group of students to integrate into the study team.
- Assisted in solving exercises and promoted group collaboration.
- Suggested ideas for improving Bootcamp processes.

CTO - Technology Manager - HOTEL UMAN HOUSE (12/2013 - 02/2018)

- Completely automated the Hotel operations.
- Implemented a CRM system and utilized newly developed technologies.
- · Provided training to staff for technology usage.
- Web Design and Application: developed the website along with the CRM and reservation system.
- Security System with cameras and electronic keycards for doors and entrances.

TECHNOLOGIES:

Programming Languages: React, JavaScript, TypeScript.

Framework Tools: Nest, ExpressJS, Angular.

Databases: MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Firebase.

Tools: Github, Slack.

Agile: Scrum.

PROFESSIONAL EDUCATION

• Full Stack Web Developer. Henry Bootcamp. 800 hours of theoretical-practical training. 2023.

Systems Analyst. Universidad U-CAECE. 1990 - 1995.

CERTIFICATES

Getting Started with MongoDB Atlas - MongoDB.com (07/2023 - 07/2023).

- EFSET English Certificate 49/100 B1 EF Set (2023 2023).
- Scrum Foundation Professional Certificate SFPC Certiprof (2023 2023).
- Firebase for Web Escuela VUE (2023 2023).
- Course in GraphQL with NodeJS Código Facilito (2023).
- Microsoft System Consultant Microsoft (2003).
- Introduction to machine learning. Udemy. (2022).
- Microsoft Desktop Support Technician Microsoft (2004).
- Microsoft System Administrator Microsoft (2003 2003). Microsoft certificates were updated (2023).

LANGUAGES

English B1 - Intermediate.